WONJONG PARK

Sammamish, WA 98029 ♦ (425) 375-5525 ♦ wonjong2@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/won-jong-park-a7a45146/

Portfolio: https://wonjong2.github.io/wonjong_portfolio_react/

GitHub: https://github.com/wonjong2

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY -

Experienced software engineer with extensive experience in the mobile telecommunication industry. From a software engineer who developed Protocol, UI and Network features in many feature phones to a project manager who handles entire mobile product lifecycle in various mobile devices, resulted in mobile products launched in markets on time with high quality and contributed to the growth of the company. Excellent reputation for resolving problems and improving customer satisfaction.

• **Professional Skills**: Project planning and management, Software development lifecycles, Software release management, Product timeline management

———— TECHNICAL SKILLS ———

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, React, SQL, MySQL, C, GitHub, Node.js, Express, Bootstrap, Foundation, Handlebars, Sequelize, Inquirer, Jest, Moment, Bcrypt, MongoDB, Mongoose, Webpack, Progressive Web App, IndexedDB, GraphQL

——— Projects ———

Driveway Myway (Group Project 3)

- A full stack application that allows a user to post or reserve available driveways to park a car
- Tech: React, Node.js, express.js, MongoDB/mongoose, GraphQL, Stripe, Google-map-react, Cloudinary, and PWA
- GitHub: https://github.com/wonjong2/Driveway-Myway
- Deployed App.: https://driveway-myway.herokuapp.com/

Ben's Diner (Group Project 2)

- A full stack web application that allows customers to view a digital menu and order food
- Tech: Node.js, express.js, express-handlebars, sequelize, MySQL2, express-session, and Bcrypt
- GitHub: https://github.com/wonjong2/Bens Diner
- Deployed App.: https://bens-diner.herokuapp.com/

Weather Dashboard

- Provide the current weather and 5 days forecast for the city that a user searches/selects
- Tech: Openweather APIs, Bootstrap, Moment.js, and JavaScript
- GitHub: https://github.com/wonjong2/Week6_Weather_Dashboard
- Deployed App.: https://wonjong2.github.io/Week6_Weather_Dashboard/

Tech Blog MVC

- A CMS-style blog site. This full stack application follows the MVC paradigm
- Tech: Node.js, express.js, express-handlebars, sequelize, MySQL2, express-session, and Bcrypt
- GitHub: https://github.com/wonjong2/Tech Blog MVC

	WORK HISTORY
Samsung Electronics An • Lead all AT&T/Cricl	neer II in MNOs Lab., October 2018 to December 2021 nerica – Bellevue, WA ket mobile projects (more than 15 new projects and 30 maintenance projects per year) ne in the U.S market by working with R&D groups, various local teams, and external
 Identify risk points by relevant teams (SW/I) Participate and support 	ights and expertise to resolve technical issues on mobile devices y checking project status / schedule and find solutions to mitigate those with all HW R&D, marketing teams, product planning team, QA team) ort the first commercial 5G phone Projects and all flagship projects in the U.S market 21, S22, N10, N20, Fold and Z-flip)
Samsung Electronics – S ● Analyze customer recustomers	neer in Dedicated AT&T Project Leader Group, March 2017 to September 2018 Suwon, S. Korea quirements / approval process and provide expertized insight to discuss with plans for more than 30 running projects with necessary changes for technical projects
 Samsung Electronics – S ◆ Lead various AT&T/ Galaxy Grand Prime, ◆ Conduct initial analy resolution 	T-Mobile mobile devices as a SW project lead - Galaxy S4, Galaxy Note Pro 12.2,
Additional Experience • Software Developed	er, Samsung Electronics, Suwon, Korea
	EDUCATION —

Participating 'The University of Washington Coding Bootcamp' (A Certificate Program for Full Stack Web Development, Feb. 2022 ~ Aug.2022)

CERTIFICATIONS —

PMP (Project Management Professional) Samsung Software Certificate - Advanced Level (2015)

• Fully Vaccinated for COVID-19 in Apr. 2021